I
I will be king
And you
you will be queen
Though nothing
will drive them
away
We can beat them
just for one day
We can be Heroes
And you
you can be mean
And I
I'll drink all
the time
Cause we're
lovers
and that is a fact
Yes we're lovers
and that is that
Though nothing
will keep us
together
We could steal
time
just for one day
We can be Heroes
for ever and ever
What d'you say?
I
I wish you
could swim
Like the dolphins
like dolphins
can swim
Though nothing
nothing will keep
us together
We can beat them
for ever and ever
Oh we can be
Heroes
just for one day
I
I will be king
And you
you will be queen
Though nothing
will drive them
away
We can be Heroes
just for one day
We can be us
I
I can remember
Standing
by the wall
And the guns
shot above
our heads
And we kissed
as though nothing
could fall
And the shame
was on the
other side
Oh we can
beat them
for ever and ever
Then we could be
Heroes
just for one day
We can be Heroes
Just for one day
We're nothing
and nothing will
help us
Maybe we're lying
then you better
not stay
But we could
be safer
just for one day